<package>
	<id>io.catto.wallpaperroller</id>
	<name>Wallpaper Roller</name>
	<version>1.0.0</version>
	<compatibility>
		<firmware>
			<miniOS>11.0</miniOS>
		</firmware>
	</compatibility>
	<dependencies>
		<package>mobilesubstrate</package>
		<package>com.matchstic.xenhtml</package>
	</dependencies>
	<shortDescription>Roll your own dynamic wallpaper</shortDescription>
	<descriptionlist>
		<description>Wallpaper Roller is a Xen HTML background that will rotate a set of images on a regular basis. You can use JPEG, PNG and even GIF and MP4 files, or use any compatible Danbooru website to pull images from the internet.</description>
		<description></description>
		<description>Installation guide:</description>
		<description><![CDATA[
		1. Install WallpaperRoller;<br/>
		2. Put your images or MP4 videos into /var/mobile/Library/WR_Pictures;<br/>
		3. Reinstall WallpaperRoller to update the image list;<br/>
		4. Add Wallpaper Roller as a background in Xen HTML settings;<br/>
		5. Enable persistent mode by going into Xen HTML lockscreen settings -> Advanced -> Turn on Persistent Mode;<br/>
		6. If desired, configure the additional settings.
		]]>
		</description>
		<description></description>
		<description>Detailed description of options:</description>
		<description><![CDATA[
		Change Interval: in minutes, how often to refresh the wallpaper. Updates only happen when the wallpaper becomes visible.<br/>
		Shake sensitivity: shake the device to immediately change the wallpaper. Smaller number: higher sensitivity.<br/>
		Enable online images: enable pulling images from a Danbooru API like e926.net<br/>
		Connection check URL: enter IP:PORT of any local WiFi device with a webserver, for example a router at 192.168.1.1:80. This will disable online images when not on WiFi. Leave blank to only use online images.<br/>
		Online API URL: Danbooru API url to poll. Must return data in the following format: {posts: [tags: ["cute", "sfw"], file: [url: "https://..."]]}<br/>
		Blacklisted tags: remove posts that have these tags. Must be comma separated, no spaces.
		]]>
		</description>
	</descriptionlist>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot>
			<description>Imagine your wallpaper here, changing regularly</description>
			<image>screenshot-1.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>		
		<screenshot>
			<description>Settings pane</description>
			<image>screenshot-2.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>		
	</screenshots>
	<changelog>
		<change>Initial release</change>
	</changelog>
	<links>
		<link>
			<name>Release post on r/iOSthemes</name>
			<url>https://www.reddit.com/r/iOSthemes</url>
			<iconclass>fa fa-reddit</iconclass>
		</link>
	</links>
</package>
